

ABOUT ME

As a highly motivated and committed web developer and graduate Engineer for Electrical Engineering and Telecommunication, you will get with me:

- Work experience in various technical fields
- Compliance with high quality standards
- On-time project delivery
- IT-driven curiosity

Out of passion for digital technology and trends, I switched my career path to programming in 2019. In order to generate more know-how, I successfully completed a full-stack Web development course based on the MERN stack at DCI. I look forward to providing you with my knowledge and analytical skills in Web development.

JavaScript

Frameworks:

React / Hooks

React Router

Redux

• Vue

Angular

¡Query

Bootstrap

Material UI

Reactstrap

Technologies:

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node.is

Databases:

- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- MySQL

Version Control:

- Git
- GitHub

LANGUAGES English (C1)

German (B2)

Serbian

Croatian

CONTACT

Hamburg

+49 174 623 15 25

alen.eftimov@gmail.com

https://github.com/Alen-Eftimov

in www.linkedin.com/in/eftimov-alen

https://www.xing.com/profile /Alen_Eftimov3/cv

Alen Eftimov

Full Stack Web Developer

EDUCATION -

2019 - 2021 Full Stack Web Developer

DCI Hamburg - DigitalCareerInstitute gGmbH

Successful completion of a one-year training course based on MERN Stack, including several practical project works

1995 - 2006

M.Sc. in Electrical and Telecommunications Engineering Faculty of Electronic Engineering Niš - University of Niš, Serbia

RELEVANT PROJECTS -

Dr.House - https://dr-house.herokuapp.com

- Multi-purpose health care website for hospitals, clinics, doctors and patients.
- Technologies used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ES6, NodeJS, EJS, Bootstrap, MongoDB

Web Shop React App - https://web-shop-app-react.netlify.app

- Frontend eCommerce application based on React.
- Technologies used: React, React Hooks, React Router, ES6, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Material UI

portfolioAlen - https://alen-eftimov-portfolio.herokuapp.com

EXPERIENCE -

2014 - 2017

Independent Designer of Telecommunication Systems -Belgrade, Serbia

- **Designing:** CCTV, alarm fire sound systems, computer, telephone and optical networks for buildings, shops and houses.
- Technologies used: AutoCad, MS Office

2013 - 2014

CEG International - Doha, Qatar

- Consultant of Telecommunications Systems for : CCTV, alarm - fire - sound systems, computers, telephone and optical networks.
- Technologies used: AutoCad, MS Office

2007 - 2013

ARHIPRO - Belgrade, Serbia

- Designer of telecommunication Systems for : CCTV, alarm - fire - sound systems, computers, telephone and optical networks in buildings, shops and houses.
- Technologies used: AutoCad, MS Office

EXPERTISE -

HOBBIES & INTERESTS -

Web development Responsive design Clean coding **Database systems** Code testing **Effective writing**

Reading **Traveling Jogging**